Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Shop Files, 1951-1998
  - Subseries V:A: General Shop Files, 1951-1998.
    - The News: Pension and Welfare Fund-Personnel 1967 (Box 259)
    - The News: Personnel 1968-1980 (Box 260)
    - The News: Photoengraver's Strike (charges and decisions) (Box 261)
    - The News: Scholarship-Union Security (Box 262)
    - The News: Unit Clarification – Welfare (Box 263)
    - The News Tribune – Newsweek: Contract (Box 264)
    - Newsweek: General 1951-1993 (Box 265)
    - Newsweek: Grievance 1953- Negotiations 1952 (Box 266)
    - Newsweek: Negotiations 1952- N/W (Shop Paper) 1970 (Box 267)
    - Newsweek: N/W (Shop Paper) 1972- Newsweek: Pension 1982 (Box 268)
    - Newsweek: Personnel 1964- North American Newspaper Alliance (Box 269)
    - Norwalk Hour- Parade (Box 270)
    - Parents – La Prensa: Grievance 1960 (Box 271)
    - La Prensa: Grievance 1961-Il Progresso: Arbitrations 1986 (Arbitrations needs to be sorted for Il Progresso) (Box 272)
    - Il Progresso: Contracts – Grievances 1976 (Box 273)
    - Il Progresso: Grievances 1977-Negotiations 1964 (Box 274)
    - Il Progresso: Negotiations 1967 – Queens Nassau Pix (Box 275)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 276)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 277)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 278)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 279)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 280)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 281)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 282)
    - Regency and Register (Box 283)
    - Reporter (Box 284)
    - Retired Members Unit (Box 285)
    - Reuters (Box 286)
    - Reuters (Box 287)
    - Reuters (Box 288)
    - Reuters (Box 289)
    - Reuters (Box 290)
    - Reuters (Box 291)
    - Reuters: Cohen & Glickstein (Box 292)
    - Reuters Arbitrations (Box 293)
    - Reuters (Box 294)
    - Reuters (Box 295)
    - Reuters (Box 296)
    - Reuters (Box 297)
    - Reuters (Box 298)
    - Reuters (Box 299)
    - Saturday Review (known as Saturday Review of Literature until 1954) (Box 300)
    - Saturday Review (known as Saturday Review of Literature until 1954) (Box 301)
    - Saturday Review (known as Saturday Review of Literature until 1954) (Box 302)
    - Scholastic (Box 303)
    - Scholastic (Box 304)
    - Scholastic (Box 305)
    - Scholastic (Box 306)
    - Scholastic (Box 307)
    - Scientific American (Box 308)
    - Scientific American (Box 309)
    - Scientific American (Box 310)
    - Scientific American (Box 311)
    - Scientific American (Box 312)
    - Show Biz, Scripps Howard, Staats-Herold (Box 313)
    - Standard & Poor's (Box 314)
    - Standard & Poor's (Box 315)
    - Standard & Poor's (Box 316)
    - Standard & Poor's (Box 317)
    - Standard & Poor's (Box 318)
    - Standard News, Staten Island Advance, Sterling Magazines, Suffolk Life (Box 319)
    - Tablet, Textile Workers Union of America, This Week, Tide, Time, Inc. (Box 320)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 321)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 322)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 323)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 324)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 325)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 326)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 327)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 328)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 329)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 330)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 331)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 332)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 333)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 334)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 335)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 336)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 337)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 338)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 339)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 340)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 341)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 342)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 343)
    - Time, Inc., Time Warner, Topics, Trade Union Service, Tribune Syndicate, Triangle Publications (Box 344)
    - Wall Street Journal (Box 345)
    - Wall Street Journal, Waterbury Republican-American (Box 346)
    - Westbury Publications, Westchester Rockland Newspapers, WGSM, Wid's Film and Film Folk, William Douglas McAdams, Wire Services (Box 347)
    - WMCA, Women's New Service, Woodbridge News Tribune (Box 348)
    - Woodbridge News Tribune, Worker, World Journal Tribune (Box 349)
    - World Journal Tribune (Box 350)
    - World Journal Tribune (Box 351)
    - World Journal Tribune (Box 352)
    - World Journal Tribune (Box 353)
    - World Telegram and Sun (Box 354)
    - World Telegram and Sun (Box 355)
    - World Telegram and Sun (Box 356)
    - World Telegram and Sun (Box 357)
    - WPIX (Box 358)
    - WPIX (Box 359)
    - WQXR (Box 360)
    - WQXR, WRN (Box 361)
  - Subseries V:B: New York Daily News Shop Files (Box 362-417)
    Access Restrictions
    These materials are unprocessed and accessible only with permission from the donor.
    - New York Daily News, 1981 (Box 362)
    - New York Daily News, 1990-1991 (Box 363)
    - New York Daily News, 1981; 1967-1968 (Box 364)
    - New York Daily News, 1979-1983 (Box 365)
    - New York Daily News, 1990-1991; 1960-1971 (Box 366)
    - New York Daily News, 1973-1981 (Box 367)
    - New York Daily News, 1990s (Box 368)
    - New York Daily News, 1990s; 1980-1981 (Box 369)
    - New York Daily News, 1978-1992 (Box 370)
    - New York Daily News, 1979-1981; 1962 (Box 371)
    - New York Daily News, 1990s (Box 372)
    - New York Daily News: Barry Lipton, 1990s (Box 373)
    - New York Daily News, 1980-1982 (Box 374)
    - New York Daily News: Arbitration, 1969-1977 (Box 375)
    - New York Daily News: Arbitration, 1955; 1953-1962 (Box 376)
    - New York Daily News, 1969-1989; bulk 1983 (Box 377)
    - New York Daily News: Arbitration, 1965-1973 (Box 378)
    - New York Daily News, 1963-1975 (Box 379)
    - New York Daily News (Strike), 1971; 1978-1979 (Box 380)
    - New York Daily News: Arbitration, 1978 (Box 381)
    - New York Daily News: NLRB and Litigation, 1991 (Box 382)
    - New York Daily News, 1979-1980 (Box 383)
    - New York Daily News, 1960s-1980s (Box 384)
    - New York Daily News, 1960s-1970s (Box 385)
    - New York Daily News: Trial Board, undated (Box 386)
    - New York Daily News, 1950s; 1974-1978 (Box 387)
    - New York Daily News, 1950s-1960s (Box 388)
    - New York Daily News: Litigation, 1980s; 1991 (Box 389)
    - New York Daily News (Strike), 1991 (Box 390)
    - New York Daily News (Strike), 1990-1991 (Box 391)
    - New York Daily News (Strike), 1990-1991 (Box 392)
    - New York Daily News (Strike); Trial Board, 1990-1991 (Box 393)
    - New York Daily News: Trial Board, 1991 (Box 394)
    - New York Daily News: Trial Board, 1991 (Box 395)
    - New York Daily News: Trial Board, 1991 (Box 396)
    - New York Daily News: Trial Board, 1991 (Box 397)
    - New York Daily News (Strike), 1990-1991 (Box 398)
    - New York Daily News: Strike Proposals, 1991 (Box 399)
    - New York Daily News (Box 400)
    - New York Daily News (Box 401)
    - New York Daily News (Box 402)
    - New York Daily News (Discharges), 1971-1974 (Box 403)
    - New York Daily News: Trial Board, 1991 (Box 404)
    - New York Daily News: Trial Board, 1991 (Box 405)
    - New York Daily News, 1950s; 1970s (Box 406)
    - New York Daily News, 1950s-1980s (Box 407)
    - New York Daily News: Litigation, 1980s (Box 408)
    - New York Daily News: Job Descriptions, undated (Box 409)
    - New York Daily News: Litigation, 1980s (Box 410)
    - New York Daily News: Litigation, 1980s (Box 411)
    - New York Daily News, 1980s (Box 412)
    - New York Daily News: Job Descriptions, 1979 (Box 413)
    - New York Daily News (Box 414)
    - New York Daily News, undated (Box 415)
    - New York Daily News, undated (Box 416)
    - New York Daily News, 1977-1979 (Box 417)
  - Subseries V:C: New York Times Shop Files (Box 418-528)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 418)
    - New York Times, 1970-1978 (Box 419)
    - New York Times, 1975-1977 (Box 420)
    - New York Times, 1976 (Box 421)
    - New York Times NLRB/ Litigation, undated (Box 422)
    - New York Times, 1977 (Box 423)
    - New York Times, 1970s (Box 424)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 425)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 426)
    - New York Times, 1960s-1980s (Box 427)
    - New York Times, 1960s-1980s (Box 428)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 429)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 430)
    - New York Times, 1975 (Box 431)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 432)
    - New York Times NLRB Transcripts, undated (Box 433)
    - New York Times NLRB Transcripts, undated (Box 434)
    - New York Times NLRB Transcripts, undated (Box 435)
    - New York Times NLRB Transcripts, undated (Box 436)
    - New York Times Negotiations, undated (Box 437)
    - New York Times Permanent Files, undated (Box 437)
    - New York Times Negotiations, undated (Box 438)
    - New York Times Negotiations, undated (Box 439)
    - New York Times Grievances, undated (Box 440)
    - New York Times Job Descriptions: I-R, undated (Box 441)
    - New York Times Job Descriptions: A-F, undated (Box 442)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 443)
    - New York Times Shop Files, undated (Box 444)
    - New York Times Shop Files, undated (Box 445)
    - New York Times Permanent Files, undated (Box 446)
    - New York Times Permanent Files, undated (Box 447)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 448)
    - New York Times Permanent Files, undated (Box 449)
    - New York Times Reslotting, undated (Box 450)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 451)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 452)
    - New York Times, Correspondence & Shop Files, undated (Box 453)
    - New York Times Unit Clarifications, undated (Box 454)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 455)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 456)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 457)
    - New York Times, 1980s (Box 458)
    - New York Times, 1970s (Box 459)
    - New York Times, 1975; 1983 (Box 460)
    - New York Times, 1980s (Box 461)
    - New York Times, 1970s (Box 462)
    - New York Times, 1980s (Box 463)
    - New York Times Litigation, 1978-1984 (Box 464)
    - New York Times Job Descriptions, 1960s; 1978-1984 (Box 465)
    - New York Times Litigation, undated (Box 466)
    - New York Times, 1979 (Box 467)
    - New York Times, 1979 (Box 468)
    - New York Times Litigation, 1970s (Box 469)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 470)
    - New York Times Trial Board, undated (Box 471)
    - New York Times Partially processed, undated (Box 472)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 473)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 474)
    - New York Times, 1959-1962 (Box 475)
    - New York Times Litigation, 1959-1962 (Box 476)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 477)
    - New York Times Partially Processed, undated (Box 478)
    - New York Times Partially Processed, undated (Box 479)
    - New York Times Partially Processed, undated (Box 480)
    - New York Times, 1965-1970 (Box 481)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 482)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 483)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 484)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 485)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 486)
    - New York Times Arbitration, undated (Box 487)
    - New York Times Partially Processed, undated (Box 488)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 489)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 490)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 491)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 492)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 493)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 494)
    - New York Times Arbitration, undated (Box 495)
    - New York Times Litigation, undated (Box 496)
    - New York Times Rosario v. New York Time, 1970s (Box 497)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 498)
    - New York Times Litigation, undated (Box 499)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 500)
    - New York Times Arbitrations, undated (Box 501)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 502)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 503)
    - New York Times Partially Processed, undated (Box 504)
    - New York Times (includes Richard Severo Files), undated (Box 505)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 506)
    - New York Times, 1982 (Box 507)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 508)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 509)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 510)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 511)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 512)
    - New York Times Arbitration, undated (Box 513)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 514)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 515)
    - New York Times, 1950s (Box 516)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 517)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 518)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 519)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 520)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 521)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 522)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 523)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 524)
    - New York Times, undated (Box 525)
    - New York Times, 1964 (Box 526)
    - New York Times Litigation, undated (Box 527)
    - New York Times Severo Legal Files, undated (Box 528)
- Series VI: Unprocessed Materials (Box 529-551)
  - Shop Files Pre-1951: [Processed] (Brooklyn Eagle) (Box 529)
  - Shop Files Pre-1951: (NY Post, PM, Parade, Overseas News Agency, Herald Tribune, The Day (Jewish Journal)) (Box 530)
  - Shop Files Pre-1951: (Journal American, Morning Journal, Journal of Commerce, Nation, NY Post, Bronx Home News) (Box 531)
  - Shop Files Pre-1951: (Editorial Publications, Daily Mirror, Jewish Day, Jewish Journal, Federated Press, Daily Compass, Fairchild, Women's Wear, Newsweek, NY Star, Newsday, Daily News, The News, Herald Tribune, NY Age) (Box 532)
  - General Files Pre-1951: (Murphy's Files, Shop Papers) (Box 533)
  - Shop Files Pre-1951: (New Republic, Journal American, In Fact, Parkchester Review, People's Voice, Look (Cowles), Long Island Star Journal, Long Island Press, New York Times), Publisher's Service (Box 534)
  - General Files Pre-1951: (Westchester Newspaper Guild, State County and Municipal Workers of America, Executive Board Minutes, Guild Organizing Material) (Box 535)
  - Shop Files Pre-1951: (Hearst National Memorandum, Morning Telegraph, Daily Mirror, New York Star, Morning Freiheit, Herald Tribune) partial box (Box 535)
  - Cartoons from Daily News Strike 1990's (Box 535)
  - General Files Pre-1951: (Westchester Newspaper Guild, State County and Municipal Workers of America, Executive Board Minutes, Guild Organizing Material) (Box 536)
  - Shop Files Pre-1951: (Hearst National Memorandum, Morning Telegraph, Daily Mirror, New York Star, Morning Freiheit, Herald Tribune) partial box (Box 536)
  - Shop Files Post-1950: (Radio Free Europe, Retired Members Unit, Reuters) (Box 537)
  - General Files Post-1950: (NLRB) (Box 538)
  - General Files Post-1950 (Box 539)
  - Shop Files Post-1950: (New York Post including strike) (Box 540)
  - Shop Files Post-1950: (N-P; S-W) (Box 541)
  - Shop Files Post-1950: (C; E-L) (Box 542)
  - Shop Files Post-1950: (A) (Box 543)
  - Shop Files Post-1950: (D) (Box 544)
  - General Files Post-1950 (Box not specified)
  - General Files Post-1950 (Box 545)
  - General Files Post-1950 (Box 546)
  - General Files Post-1950: (Officer's Correspondence 1980-1982, General) (Box 547)
  - General Files Post-1950: (Visual Display Terminals) (Box 548)
  - General Files Post (Box 549)
  - General Files Post (Box 550)
  - General Files Post (Box 551)
  - Unprocessed (Box 1)
  - Ephemera, 1939-1950 (Box 552, Folder 89)
- Series VII: Photographs, 1940-1950
  Series VII: Photographs, contains images of numerous NGNY strikes, negotiations proceedings, and elections held during the 1940s.
  - The Bell Syndicate: Strike Publicity, May 1949 (Box 552, Folder 1)
  - Citywide Negotiations (includes description), Apr. 6, 1943 (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Guild Unity Advertisement, Dec. 1947 (Box OS 001)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) War Chest, undated (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Elections: Left Wing Opposition, undated (Box 552, Folder 4)
  - Elections: Left Wing Opposition (negatives), undated (Box 552, Folder 5)
  - Elections: Left Wing Opposition Box, circa 1948-1950 (Box 552, Folder 6)
  - Empire State District Council Luncheon: College Newspaper Awards, 1965 (Box 552, Folder 7)
  - General, 1944 (Box 552, Folder 8)
  - Greater New York Fund: City Wide Report Luncheon (Thomas J. Murphy, M. Michael Potoker), 1953 (Box 552, Folder 9)
  - Guild Club, House Committee, 1944, undated (Box 552, Folder 10)
  - The Guild Parade of 1940 Advertisement (Box 552, Folder 11)
  - Guild Shop News Bulletins, Oct. 1941-Dec. 1941 (Box 552, Folder 12)
  - Guildsmen at an Informal National Meeting, circa 1962-1963 (Box 552, Folder 13)
  - Leaflet, 1941 (Box 552, Folder 14)
  - Magazine Management, Company, circa 1970-1979 (Box 552, Folder 15)
  - Municipal Photographers Fact Finding Hearing: City of New York Department of Sanitation, 1957 (Box 552, Folder 16)
  - Municipal Photographers Fact Finding Hearing: New York City Police Athletic League Group Publicity Photo, 1957-circa 1965 (Box 552, Folder 17)
  - Municipal Photographers Fact Finding Hearing: New York City Police Helicopter and Boat Rescue, 1957-circa 1964 (Box 552, Folder 18)
  - Municipal Photographers Fact Finding Hearing: "Soft Cushion Water Bumper" Staged Bus and Truck "Fender-Popper", 1957-circa 1964 (Box 552, Folder 19)
  - Municipal Photographers Fact Finding Hearing: Ticker Tape Parade, 1957-circa 1964 (Box 552, Folder 20)
  - Municipal Photographers Fact Finding Hearing: United Airlines Flight 826 Wreckage at Seventh Avenue and Sterling Place, 1960 (Box 552, Folder 21)
  - New York Daily News: Storefront, 1966 (Box 552, Folder 22)
  - New York Post: Unidentified Woman at Newsroom Desk, circa 1960-1969 (Box 552, Folder 23)
  - The News Syndicate Photographers, 1949 (Box 552, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, Vancouver, 1988 (Box 552, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Guild Headquarters (West 43 Street), circa 1940s, undated (Box 552, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Guild New York and ANG Officers in Front of Heywood Broun Painting, 1960 (Box 552, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Guild New York Officers with Microphone, 1959 (Box 552, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Guild New York and ANG Officers in Front of Guild Banner, late 1950s-early 1960s (Box 552, Folder 29)
  - Newsstand Dealers Union, Local 217, 1947-1948 (Box 552, Folder 30)
  - New York Times Collective Bargaining, 1941 (Box 552, Folder 31)
  - New York Times Negotiations Advertisement, 1941 (Box 552, Folder 32)
  - New York Times Negotiations with National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1941 (Box 552, Folder 33)
  - Office of War Information Films, 1944 (Box 552, Folder 34)
  - 119th Convention in Cincinnati, Ohio, 1977 (Box 552, Folder 35)
  - Page One Ball: Adams, Edie, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 36)
  - Page One Ball: Albanese, Licia, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 37)
  - Page One Ball: Alda, Robert, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 38)
  - Page One Ball: Arden, Toni and Jan, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 39)
  - Page One Ball: Buttons, Red, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 40)
  - Page One Ball: Deegan, John E. and Nancy O'Sullivan, 1975 (Box 552, Folder 41)
  - Page One Ball: Dishy, Bob, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 42)
  - Page One Ball: Dunn, Michael and Phoebe Dorin, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 43)
  - Page One Ball: Galamb, Attila, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 44)
  - Page One Ball: Golonka, Arlene, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 45)
  - Page One Ball: Griffin, Merv, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 46)
  - Page One Ball: Guinness, Abe, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 47)
  - Page One Ball: Hayes, Bill, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 48)
  - Page One Ball: Hildegarde, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 49)
  - Page One Ball: Jessel, George, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 50)
  - Page One Ball: Keller, Ben, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 51)
  - Page One Ball: Kelly, Al, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 52)
  - Page One Ball: Klemesrud, Judy, 1976 (Box 552, Folder 53)
  - Page One Ball: Lansing, Joi, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 54)
  - Page One Ball: McGuire, Phyllis, Christine, and Dorothy, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 55)
  - Page One Ball: McNickle, George, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 56)
  - Page One Ball: Meader, Vaughn, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 57)
  - Page One Ball: Miss Page One and Her Court, 1965 (Box 552, Folder 58)
  - Page One Ball: Montgomery, Marian, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 59)
  - Page One Ball: Newspaper Guild New York Officers, 1953 (Box 552, Folder 60)
  - Page One Ball: Reilly, Charles Nelson, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 61)
  - Page One Ball: Schaal, Dick, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 62)
  - Page One Ball: Schreiber, Avery, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 63)
  - Page One Ball: Sedaka, Neil, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 64)
  - Page One Ball: Serrano, Juan, 1965 (Box 552, Folder 65)
  - Page One Ball: Sheperd, Jean, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 66)
  - Page One Ball: Stricker, Lorena, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 67)
  - Page One Ball: Taylor, Rip, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 68)
  - Page One Ball: Thomas, Andy, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 69)
  - Page One Ball: Vale, Jerry, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 70)
  - Page One Ball: Vallee, Rudy and Hickman, Danye, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 71)
  - Page One Ball: Van Vooren, Monique, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 72)
  - Page One Ball: Wilson, Julie, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 73)
  - Page One Ball: Wyler, Gretchen, 1964 (Box 552, Folder 74)
  - The People's Voice, circa 1947 (Box 552, Folder 75)
  - PM Staff Meeting, Mar. 15, 1948 (Box 552, Folder 76)
  - St. Louis Post Dispatch: "Atrocity Murals" (includes descriptions), 1945 (Box 552, Folder 77)
  - Strikes: Brooklyn Eagle, 1955 (Box 552, Folder 78)
  - Strikes: Handpainted Sign Posted on Door of New York Times, Nov 30, 1953 (Box 552, Folder 79)
  - Strikes: New York Daily News Strike Benefit, 1990 (Box 552, Folder 80)
  - Strikes: New York Post: "Don't Waltz With Matilda", 1978 (Box 552, Folder 81)
  - Strikes: New York Post: Pickets Outside New York Post Building at South Street, 1970 (Box 552, Folder 82)
  - Ta Kung Pao, Chungking Air Raid Shelter, Cellar Printing Plant, circa 1940 (Box 552, Folder 83)
  - Time Inc. Negotiations, circa 1946 (Box 552, Folder 84)
  - Ukrainian Journalists, undated (Box 552, Folder 85)
  - Unidentified Photographs, undated (Box 552, Folder 86-87)
  - Women's Auxiliary, 1943 (Box 552, Folder 88)
  - Daily News videos: Intimidation of news dealer footage, 1990-11-08 (Box Shared Tamiment 013, Cassette 6-7)
- Series VIII: Archived Website, Feb 5, 2009-ongoing
  The Newspaper Guild of New York, launched in 1934, is an labor union for people in the news and media business, including print, photo, video, and digital journalists, as well as employees in advertising, circulation and other related areas. They represent about 3,000 employees at New York area-based media organizations and their respective bureaus around the nation. The website contains information on current bureaus represented by the union and news listings.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.